{
  "uniqueId": "english definitions 1",
  "name": "English Vocabulary Quiz",
  "article": "an",
  "instructions": "Guess the word!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "TEXT_WITH_HINT",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "WEBSTER_ANSWER",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "WITH_HINT",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "BETTER_ENGLISH_DEFINITIONS",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "ANSWER_ONLY",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "on a small scale",
      "answer": "small"
    },
    {
      "question": "as much as necessary",
      "answer": "enough"
    },
    {
      "question": "be without, lack",
      "answer": "want"
    },
    {
      "question": "take sides for or against",
      "answer": "side"
    },
    {
      "question": "a female person who plays a significant role (wife or mistress or girlfriend) in the life of a particular man",
      "answer": "woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "in whatever way or manner",
      "answer": "however"
    },
    {
      "question": "to the fullest extent",
      "answer": "home"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who holds an important or distinguished position in some organization",
      "answer": "father"
    },
    {
      "question": "actually or truly or to an extreme",
      "answer": "quite"
    },
    {
      "question": "language that is spoken or written",
      "answer": "words"
    },
    {
      "question": "acknowledged as a supposition",
      "answer": "given"
    },
    {
      "question": "work land as by ploughing, harrowing, and manuring, in order to make it ready for cultivation",
      "answer": "till"
    },
    {
      "question": "be affected with an indisposition",
      "answer": "taken"
    },
    {
      "question": "habitually do something (use only in the past tense)",
      "answer": "use"
    },
    {
      "question": "(with `in') guardianship over",
      "answer": "hands"
    },
    {
      "question": "put an end to",
      "answer": "end"
    },
    {
      "question": "moved around an axis or center  ",
      "answer": "turned"
    },
    {
      "question": "to some (great or small) extent",
      "answer": "rather"
    },
    {
      "question": "it would be sensible",
      "answer": "best"
    },
    {
      "question": "change texture so as to become matted and felt-like",
      "answer": "felt"
    },
    {
      "question": "a word is a string of bits stored in computer memory",
      "answer": "word"
    },
    {
      "question": "employed in accomplishing something",
      "answer": "used"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of sleep) easily disturbed",
      "answer": "light"
    },
    {
      "question": "at the time or occasion immediately following",
      "answer": "next"
    },
    {
      "question": "comparative of little",
      "answer": "less"
    },
    {
      "question": " being or existing in a specified place",
      "answer": "present"
    },
    {
      "question": "with the wind abaft the beam",
      "answer": "large"
    },
    {
      "question": "fill with tears",
      "answer": "water"
    },
    {
      "question": "a room that is comfortable and secluded  ",
      "answer": "den"
    },
    {
      "question": "a room that is entered via a door",
      "answer": "door"
    },
    {
      "question": "unsatisfactory",
      "answer": "poor"
    },
    {
      "question": "exercising or taking care great enough to bring assurance",
      "answer": "certain"
    },
    {
      "question": "the internal mechanism of a device  ",
      "answer": "works"
    },
    {
      "question": "(ballet) a step in dancing (especially in classical ballet)  ",
      "answer": "pas"
    },
    {
      "question": "caused or enabled to go or be conveyed or transmitted  ",
      "answer": "sent"
    },
    {
      "question": "in many cases or instances  ",
      "answer": "often"
    },
    {
      "question": "supply the force or power for the functioning of",
      "answer": "power"
    },
    {
      "question": "the people who are present in a room",
      "answer": "room"
    },
    {
      "question": "partially or to the extent of a half",
      "answer": "half"
    },
    {
      "question": "affecting the people or community as a whole",
      "answer": "public"
    },
    {
      "question": "the time period between dawn and noon",
      "answer": "morning"
    },
    {
      "question": "hold and prevent from leaving",
      "answer": "keep"
    },
    {
      "question": "the official currency issued by a government or national bank",
      "answer": "money"
    },
    {
      "question": "care for like a mother",
      "answer": "mother"
    },
    {
      "question": "being ten more than ninety  ",
      "answer": "hundred"
    },
    {
      "question": "tolerant and forgiving under provocation",
      "answer": "kind"
    },
    {
      "question": "place in a certain order",
      "answer": "order"
    },
    {
      "question": "make or wage war  ",
      "answer": "war"
    },
    {
      "question": "considerable capital (wealth or income)",
      "answer": "means"
    },
    {
      "question": "assume a form or shape",
      "answer": "form"
    },
    {
      "question": "rain heavily",
      "answer": "pour"
    },
    {
      "question": "from beginning to end",
      "answer": "round"
    },
    {
      "question": "widely accepted as true or worthy",
      "answer": "received"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter with vibrating vocal chords  ",
      "answer": "voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "credit with veracity",
      "answer": "believe"
    },
    {
      "question": "of summer nights in northern latitudes where the sun barely sets",
      "answer": "white"
    },
    {
      "question": "near in time or place or relationship",
      "answer": "near"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the way indicated",
      "answer": "thus"
    },
    {
      "question": "written works (especially in books or magazines)",
      "answer": "matter"
    },
    {
      "question": "the period of time that it takes for a planet (as, e.g., Earth or Mars) to make a complete revolution around the sun",
      "answer": "year"
    },
    {
      "question": "to hear and understand",
      "answer": "read"
    },
    {
      "question": "as acknowledged",
      "answer": "true"
    },
    {
      "question": "repair the joints of bricks",
      "answer": "point"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person you know well and regard with affection and trust",
      "answer": "friend"
    },
    {
      "question": "express in words",
      "answer": "state"
    },
    {
      "question": "a grammatical category used in the classification of pronouns, possessive determiners, and verb forms according to whether they indicate the speaker, the addressee, or a third party",
      "answer": "person"
    },
    {
      "question": "a married woman",
      "answer": "wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "prior to a specified or implied time",
      "answer": "already"
    },
    {
      "question": "in or to a place that is higher  ",
      "answer": "above"
    },
    {
      "question": "far up toward the source",
      "answer": "high"
    },
    {
      "question": "with cooperation and interchange",
      "answer": "together"
    },
    {
      "question": "the cause or intention underlying an action or situation, especially in the phrase `the whys and wherefores'  ",
      "answer": "why"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of killing",
      "answer": "death"
    },
    {
      "question": "earnest",
      "answer": "dear"
    },
    {
      "question": "a concept whose truth can be proved",
      "answer": "fact"
    },
    {
      "question": "used to form the superlative",
      "answer": "least"
    },
    {
      "question": "look over, usually with the intention to rob",
      "answer": "case"
    },
    {
      "question": "receive a communication from someone",
      "answer": "hear"
    },
    {
      "question": "apprehended with certainty",
      "answer": "known"
    },
    {
      "question": "being one more than three  ",
      "answer": "four"
    },
    {
      "question": "intend with some possibility of fulfilment",
      "answer": "hope"
    },
    {
      "question": "in line with a length or direction (often followed by `by' or `beside')",
      "answer": "along"
    },
    {
      "question": "be survived by after one's death",
      "answer": "leave"
    },
    {
      "question": "certain not to fail",
      "answer": "sure"
    },
    {
      "question": "ready for business",
      "answer": "open"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used as an interjection) an expression of surprise or skepticism or irony etc.",
      "answer": "indeed"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used to introduce a logical conclusion) from that fact or reason or as a result",
      "answer": "therefore"
    },
    {
      "question": "place a limit on the number of  ",
      "answer": "number"
    },
    {
      "question": "invoke upon",
      "answer": "wish"
    },
    {
      "question": "a friendly informal reference to a grown woman",
      "answer": "girl"
    },
    {
      "question": "not of or from a profession",
      "answer": "lay"
    },
    {
      "question": "after a negative statement used as an intensive meaning something like `likewise' or `also'",
      "answer": "either"
    },
    {
      "question": "occupied or in the control of",
      "answer": "held"
    },
    {
      "question": "mark letters on or mark with letters  ",
      "answer": "letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "improve",
      "answer": "help"
    },
    {
      "question": "not literal",
      "answer": "free"
    },
    {
      "question": "somewhat indefinite",
      "answer": "general"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the second place",
      "answer": "second"
    },
    {
      "question": "without anybody else or anything else",
      "answer": "alone"
    },
    {
      "question": "submit (a report, etc.) to someone in authority",
      "answer": "return"
    },
    {
      "question": "a particular type of thing",
      "answer": "nature"
    },
    {
      "question": "a more or less definite period of time now or previously present",
      "answer": "times"
    },
    {
      "question": "arrive on shore",
      "answer": "land"
    },
    {
      "question": "enhance the appearance of",
      "answer": "become"
    },
    {
      "question": "denoting a quantity consisting of 1,000 items or units  ",
      "answer": "thousand"
    },
    {
      "question": "invest with or as with a body",
      "answer": "body"
    },
    {
      "question": "expose to warm or heated air, so as to dry",
      "answer": "air"
    },
    {
      "question": "rouse somebody from sleep with a call",
      "answer": "call"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a characteristic or natural sound",
      "answer": "speak"
    },
    {
      "question": "distance measured by the time taken to cover it",
      "answer": "hour"
    },
    {
      "question": "think logically",
      "answer": "reason"
    },
    {
      "question": "out into view",
      "answer": "forth"
    },
    {
      "question": "pass one's hands over the sexual organs of",
      "answer": "feel"
    },
    {
      "question": "appearing to be as specified",
      "answer": "looking"
    },
    {
      "question": "going or proceeding or coming after in the same direction",
      "answer": "following"
    },
    {
      "question": "be inactive, refrain from acting",
      "answer": "rest"
    },
    {
      "question": "incidental activity performed by an actor for dramatic effect",
      "answer": "business"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or concerned with electrons",
      "answer": "electronic"
    },
    {
      "question": "in debt",
      "answer": "behind"
    },
    {
      "question": "(usually plural) the components needed for making or doing something",
      "answer": "making"
    },
    {
      "question": "involving advantage or good",
      "answer": "plus"
    },
    {
      "question": "a member of a clan or tribe",
      "answer": "child"
    },
    {
      "question": "not caught with the senses or the mind",
      "answer": "lost"
    },
    {
      "question": "having human form or attributes as opposed to those of animals or divine beings",
      "answer": "human"
    },
    {
      "question": "being one more than four  ",
      "answer": "five"
    },
    {
      "question": "(chess) the weakest but the most important piece  ",
      "answer": "king"
    },
    {
      "question": "distinct or separate",
      "answer": "different"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide care for",
      "answer": "care"
    },
    {
      "question": "drive out or away by or as if by fire",
      "answer": "fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "at a disadvantage",
      "answer": "short"
    },
    {
      "question": "a kind",
      "answer": "manner"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of persons or behavior) characterized by or indicative of lack of generosity",
      "answer": "mean"
    },
    {
      "question": "people living in a large densely populated municipality",
      "answer": "city"
    },
    {
      "question": "sew a seam by folding the edges  ",
      "answer": "fell"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a strong healthy body",
      "answer": "able"
    },
    {
      "question": "have or feel a need for",
      "answer": "need"
    },
    {
      "question": "pose a question  ",
      "answer": "question"
    },
    {
      "question": "an association of people who share common beliefs or activities",
      "answer": "family"
    },
    {
      "question": "(ethnic slur) offensive and disparaging term for Black man",
      "answer": "boy"
    },
    {
      "question": "give rise to",
      "answer": "cause"
    },
    {
      "question": "freshly made or left",
      "answer": "strong"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a score (on a hole) equal to par  ",
      "answer": "par"
    },
    {
      "question": "being one more than nine  ",
      "answer": "ten"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of happening or existing",
      "answer": "possible"
    },
    {
      "question": "devoid of activity",
      "answer": "dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "induce or persuade",
      "answer": "bring"
    },
    {
      "question": "not recorded",
      "answer": "live"
    },
    {
      "question": "in circumference",
      "answer": "around"
    },
    {
      "question": "lack confidence in or have doubts about",
      "answer": "doubt"
    },
    {
      "question": "to the full extent possible",
      "answer": "hard"
    },
    {
      "question": "a secular form of gospel that was a major Black musical genre in the 1960s and 1970s",
      "answer": "soul"
    },
    {
      "question": "require or ask for as a price or condition",
      "answer": "ask"
    },
    {
      "question": "an operation that segregates items into groups according to a specified criterion",
      "answer": "sort"
    },
    {
      "question": "free from impurities",
      "answer": "fine"
    },
    {
      "question": "keep from exhaling or expelling",
      "answer": "hold"
    },
    {
      "question": "a polite name for any woman",
      "answer": "lady"
    },
    {
      "question": "soiled with dirt or soot",
      "answer": "black"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of weather) highly enjoyable",
      "answer": "beautiful"
    },
    {
      "question": "comprehend",
      "answer": "sense"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an attentive manner",
      "answer": "close"
    },
    {
      "question": "likely to be affected by something",
      "answer": "subject"
    },
    {
      "question": "become officially one year older",
      "answer": "turn"
    },
    {
      "question": "the people living in a municipality smaller than a city",
      "answer": "town"
    },
    {
      "question": "the learned profession that is mastered by graduate study in a law school and that is responsible for the judicial system",
      "answer": "law"
    },
    {
      "question": "the early part of night (from dinner until bedtime) spent in a special way",
      "answer": "evening"
    },
    {
      "question": "a true statement",
      "answer": "truth"
    },
    {
      "question": "connect to a ground",
      "answer": "ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "believe to be the case",
      "answer": "understand"
    },
    {
      "question": "finish third or better in a horse or dog race",
      "answer": "show"
    },
    {
      "question": "systematically collected and written down",
      "answer": "written"
    },
    {
      "question": "to be expected",
      "answer": "common"
    },
    {
      "question": "be uneasy or apprehensive about",
      "answer": "fear"
    },
    {
      "question": "not giving performances",
      "answer": "dark"
    },
    {
      "question": "have or participate in a party",
      "answer": "party"
    },
    {
      "question": "made suitable and available for immediate use",
      "answer": "ready"
    },
    {
      "question": "do forcibly",
      "answer": "force"
    },
    {
      "question": "in good time",
      "answer": "early"
    },
    {
      "question": "express in speech",
      "answer": "talk"
    },
    {
      "question": "furnish a justifying analysis or explanation",
      "answer": "account"
    },
    {
      "question": "react to a stimulus or command",
      "answer": "answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by the reception of pay",
      "answer": "paid"
    },
    {
      "question": "transversely",
      "answer": "across"
    },
    {
      "question": "unavoidably determined by prior circumstances",
      "answer": "necessary"
    },
    {
      "question": "on certain occasions or in certain cases but not always",
      "answer": "sometimes"
    },
    {
      "question": "connect to the earth",
      "answer": "earth"
    },
    {
      "question": "infuse with spirit",
      "answer": "spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "a word or phrase that particular people use in particular situations",
      "answer": "saying"
    },
    {
      "question": "a personal view",
      "answer": "idea"
    },
    {
      "question": "engrave or inscribe characters on  ",
      "answer": "character"
    },
    {
      "question": "secure a copyright on a written work",
      "answer": "copyright"
    },
    {
      "question": "turbulent water with swells of considerable size",
      "answer": "sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "a truck with an enclosed cargo space  ",
      "answer": "van"
    },
    {
      "question": "take aim by looking through the sights of a gun (or other device)  ",
      "answer": "sight"
    },
    {
      "question": "excite the curiosity of",
      "answer": "interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "denoting a quantity consisting of six items or units  ",
      "answer": "six"
    },
    {
      "question": "register in a hotel booker  ",
      "answer": "book"
    },
    {
      "question": "appear to one's own mind or opinion",
      "answer": "seem"
    },
    {
      "question": "without stop or interruption",
      "answer": "continued"
    },
    {
      "question": "support consisting of a radial member of a wheel joining the hub to the rim  ",
      "answer": "spoke"
    },
    {
      "question": "not known before",
      "answer": "strange"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a replica of",
      "answer": "copy"
    },
    {
      "question": "make older",
      "answer": "age"
    },
    {
      "question": "experience as a reaction",
      "answer": "meet"
    },
    {
      "question": "for more time",
      "answer": "longer"
    },
    {
      "question": "a piece of fiction that narrates a chain of related events",
      "answer": "story"
    },
    {
      "question": "to a great distance",
      "answer": "deep"
    },
    {
      "question": "reinforce with fabric",
      "answer": "line"
    },
    {
      "question": "in addition or furthermore",
      "answer": "further"
    },
    {
      "question": "an intuitive understanding of something",
      "answer": "feeling"
    },
    {
      "question": "comparative of the adverb `late'",
      "answer": "later"
    },
    {
      "question": "happening unexpectedly",
      "answer": "suddenly"
    },
    {
      "question": "term of address for a man  ",
      "answer": "sir"
    },
    {
      "question": "used as a term of address for those male persons engaged in the same movement",
      "answer": "brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "not either",
      "answer": "neither"
    },
    {
      "question": "be available for stud services",
      "answer": "stand"
    },
    {
      "question": "a superior skill that you can learn by study and practice and observation",
      "answer": "art"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of property) fixed or immovable",
      "answer": "real"
    },
    {
      "question": "of something having a dusty purplish pink color",
      "answer": "rose"
    },
    {
      "question": "in addition",
      "answer": "beyond"
    },
    {
      "question": "anew",
      "answer": "again"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used ironically) unexpectedly bad",
      "answer": "pretty"
    },
    {
      "question": "perform on a stage or theater",
      "answer": "act"
    },
    {
      "question": "express a supposition",
      "answer": "suppose"
    },
    {
      "question": "arrange or enter in tabular form  ",
      "answer": "table"
    },
    {
      "question": "an indefinite period of time",
      "answer": "hours"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large natural stream of water (larger than a creek)",
      "answer": "river"
    },
    {
      "question": "mixed with water",
      "answer": "cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "look at  ",
      "answer": "eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove or replace the coverings of",
      "answer": "change"
    },
    {
      "question": "earlier than the present time",
      "answer": "past"
    },
    {
      "question": "common sense",
      "answer": "nous"
    },
    {
      "question": "being talented through inherited qualities",
      "answer": "natural"
    },
    {
      "question": "not at all or in no way",
      "answer": "none"
    },
    {
      "question": "well expressed and to the point",
      "answer": "happy"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to be in an appropriate place, state, or relation  ",
      "answer": "position"
    },
    {
      "question": "completely",
      "answer": "clear"
    },
    {
      "question": "at an advanced age or stage",
      "answer": "late"
    },
    {
      "question": "put to bed",
      "answer": "bed"
    },
    {
      "question": "set down according to a plan:\"a carefully laid table with places set for four people\"",
      "answer": "laid"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking the warmth of life",
      "answer": "cold"
    },
    {
      "question": "not working properly",
      "answer": "bad"
    },
    {
      "question": "thorough",
      "answer": "sound"
    },
    {
      "question": "exercise, or have the power of, memory",
      "answer": "remember"
    },
    {
      "question": "look at carefully",
      "answer": "view"
    },
    {
      "question": "a motive for living",
      "answer": "life"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a low position",
      "answer": "low"
    },
    {
      "question": "adjust so that a force is applied and an action occurs at the desired time",
      "answer": "time"
    },
    {
      "question": "at or to or toward the front",
      "answer": "forward"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of hair or skin) pale or light-colored",
      "answer": "fair"
    },
    {
      "question": "reach a decision",
      "answer": "purpose"
    },
    {
      "question": "still in active use",
      "answer": "living"
    },
    {
      "question": "discharge or settle",
      "answer": "pay"
    },
    {
      "question": "regard favorably or with disapproval",
      "answer": "receive"
    },
    {
      "question": "smear with blood, as in a hunting initiation rite, where the face of a person is smeared with the blood of the kill  ",
      "answer": "blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large number of people united for some specific purpose  ",
      "answer": "army"
    },
    {
      "question": "a female human offspring",
      "answer": "daughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a written note of",
      "answer": "note"
    },
    {
      "question": "made open or clear",
      "answer": "opened"
    },
    {
      "question": "become undone",
      "answer": "run"
    },
    {
      "question": "come as if by falling",
      "answer": "fall"
    },
    {
      "question": "act so as to bring into existence",
      "answer": "effect"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to pass",
      "answer": "pass"
    },
    {
      "question": "expose to the rays of the sun or affect by exposure to the sun",
      "answer": "sun"
    },
    {
      "question": "a way or means to achieve something",
      "answer": "road"
    },
    {
      "question": "a married man",
      "answer": "husband"
    },
    {
      "question": "saturate",
      "answer": "charge"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or suggesting a consciousness of high position",
      "answer": "important"
    },
    {
      "question": "desired or wished for or sought",
      "answer": "wanted"
    },
    {
      "question": "the performance of duties by a waiter or servant",
      "answer": "service"
    },
    {
      "question": "confront bodily",
      "answer": "front"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a color at the end of the color spectrum (next to orange)",
      "answer": "red"
    },
    {
      "question": "with considerable certainty",
      "answer": "probably"
    },
    {
      "question": "a verb tense or other formation referring to events or states that have not yet happened",
      "answer": "future"
    },
    {
      "question": "put in position in relation to other things",
      "answer": "placed"
    },
    {
      "question": "the hollow spine of a feather  ",
      "answer": "quill"
    },
    {
      "question": "express a desire for  ",
      "answer": "desire"
    },
    {
      "question": "transfer",
      "answer": "send"
    },
    {
      "question": "a religious rite or service prescribed by ecclesiastical authorities",
      "answer": "office"
    },
    {
      "question": "greater in size or importance or degree",
      "answer": "greater"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a major way",
      "answer": "big"
    },
    {
      "question": "scholarly attainment",
      "answer": "letters"
    },
    {
      "question": "a treaty to cease hostilities",
      "answer": "peace"
    },
    {
      "question": "a filamentous projection or process on an organism  ",
      "answer": "hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "sexual gratification",
      "answer": "pleasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide with a horse or horses  ",
      "answer": "horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "feeling happy appreciation",
      "answer": "glad"
    },
    {
      "question": "the reason for a court's judgment (as opposed to the decision itself)  ",
      "answer": "opinion"
    },
    {
      "question": "all that is remembered of the past as preserved in writing",
      "answer": "history"
    },
    {
      "question": "exhaust by allowing to pull on the line",
      "answer": "play"
    },
    {
      "question": "the verbal act of agreeing  ",
      "answer": "agreement"
    },
    {
      "question": "advertize in strongly positive terms",
      "answer": "tout"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a wild or undomesticated manner",
      "answer": "wild"
    },
    {
      "question": "(government) the system or form by which a community or other political unit is governed",
      "answer": "government"
    },
    {
      "question": "spend sparingly, avoid the waste of",
      "answer": "save"
    },
    {
      "question": "a section of something that is long and narrow",
      "answer": "length"
    },
    {
      "question": "have a firm understanding or knowledge of",
      "answer": "master"
    },
    {
      "question": "the second of two or the second mentioned of two",
      "answer": "latter"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pass between mountain peaks  ",
      "answer": "col"
    },
    {
      "question": "almost not",
      "answer": "hardly"
    },
    {
      "question": "made from or covered with gold",
      "answer": "gold"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover with paper",
      "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "first and most important",
      "answer": "particular"
    },
    {
      "question": "make or leave a mark on",
      "answer": "mark"
    },
    {
      "question": "(communication theory) a numerical measure of the uncertainty of an outcome",
      "answer": "information"
    },
    {
      "question": "have rightfully",
      "answer": "bear"
    },
    {
      "question": "an informal form of address for a man",
      "answer": "fellow"
    },
    {
      "question": "perform a special church rite or service for",
      "answer": "church"
    },
    {
      "question": "a motionless erect stance with arms at the sides and feet together",
      "answer": "attention"
    },
    {
      "question": "(followed by `to') as reported or stated by",
      "answer": "according"
    },
    {
      "question": "coil the spring of (some mechanical device) by turning a stem",
      "answer": "wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "be a companion to somebody  ",
      "answer": "company"
    },
    {
      "question": "the condition of financial success",
      "answer": "strength"
    },
    {
      "question": "completely given to or absorbed by",
      "answer": "all"
    },
    {
      "question": "a man of refinement  ",
      "answer": "gentleman"
    },
    {
      "question": "lay mines",
      "answer": "mine"
    },
    {
      "question": "be averse to or express disapproval of",
      "answer": "object"
    },
    {
      "question": "a government tax on imports or exports",
      "answer": "duty"
    },
    {
      "question": "existing alone or consisting of one entity or part or aspect or individual",
      "answer": "single"
    },
    {
      "question": "keep at a distance",
      "answer": "distance"
    },
    {
      "question": "sell",
      "answer": "deal"
    },
    {
      "question": "assail",
      "answer": "visit"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide with workers",
      "answer": "man"
    },
    {
      "question": "add a column of numbers  ",
      "answer": "foot"
    },
    {
      "question": "an outstanding example of its kind",
      "answer": "beauty"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of starting something",
      "answer": "beginning"
    },
    {
      "question": "slowly as if burdened by much weight",
      "answer": "heavy"
    },
    {
      "question": "permanent",
      "answer": "standing"
    },
    {
      "question": "the process of using your mind to consider something carefully",
      "answer": "thinking"
    },
    {
      "question": "sing or play against other voices or parts",
      "answer": "carry"
    },
    {
      "question": "bearing an immediate relation",
      "answer": "immediately"
    },
    {
      "question": "the base of the natural system of logarithms",
      "answer": "e"
    },
    {
      "question": "melt (fat or lard) in order to separate out impurities",
      "answer": "try"
    },
    {
      "question": "pleasantly full and mellow",
      "answer": "rich"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking embellishment or ornamentation",
      "answer": "plain"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of wines) having a high residual sugar content",
      "answer": "sweet"
    },
    {
      "question": "having vision, not blind  ",
      "answer": "seeing"
    },
    {
      "question": "a written account of what transpired at a meeting  ",
      "answer": "minutes"
    },
    {
      "question": "grasp the meaning",
      "answer": "follow"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause bodily suffering to and make sick or indisposed  ",
      "answer": "trouble"
    },
    {
      "question": "create code, write a computer program",
      "answer": "write"
    },
    {
      "question": "be the case by chance",
      "answer": "chance"
    },
    {
      "question": "look at attentively  ",
      "answer": "regard"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of time) taken up",
      "answer": "filled"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of being present  ",
      "answer": "presence"
    },
    {
      "question": "and nothing more",
      "answer": "merely"
    },
    {
      "question": "the next to highest level of official classification for documents  ",
      "answer": "secret"
    },
    {
      "question": "the first of two or the first mentioned of two",
      "answer": "former"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small pond of standing water  ",
      "answer": "mere"
    },
    {
      "question": "present oneself formally, as before a (judicial) authority",
      "answer": "appear"
    },
    {
      "question": "supply with arms",
      "answer": "arm"
    },
    {
      "question": "disposing of property by voluntary transfer without receiving value in return",
      "answer": "giving"
    },
    {
      "question": "have and exert influence or effect",
      "answer": "influence"
    },
    {
      "question": "apply conditioner to in order to make smooth and shiny",
      "answer": "condition"
    },
    {
      "question": "denoting a quantity consisting of 20 items or units  ",
      "answer": "twenty"
    },
    {
      "question": "arrive at a certain condition through repeated motion",
      "answer": "work"
    },
    {
      "question": "(computer science) a rectangular part of a computer screen that contains a display different from the rest of the screen  ",
      "answer": "window"
    },
    {
      "question": "having feelings of aversion or unwillingness",
      "answer": "afraid"
    },
    {
      "question": "(in writing) see below",
      "answer": "below"
    },
    {
      "question": "used of the side of cloth or clothing intended to face inward",
      "answer": "wrong"
    },
    {
      "question": "a period of opportunity",
      "answer": "day"
    },
    {
      "question": "keep from expression, for example by threats or pressure",
      "answer": "silence"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking a part or parts",
      "answer": "broken"
    },
    {
      "question": "located or moved above the surround or above the normal position",
      "answer": "raised"
    },
    {
      "question": "(chiefly British) of or appropriate to the upper classes especially in language use  ",
      "answer": "u"
    },
    {
      "question": "on the outside",
      "answer": "outside"
    },
    {
      "question": "unornamented",
      "answer": "simple"
    },
    {
      "question": "understand",
      "answer": "figure"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the past",
      "answer": "ago"
    },
    {
      "question": "reach a goal, e.g., \"make the first team\"",
      "answer": "reach"
    },
    {
      "question": "without question",
      "answer": "easily"
    },
    {
      "question": "inert especially toward oxygen",
      "answer": "noble"
    },
    {
      "question": "very old",
      "answer": "ancient"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing dejection",
      "answer": "blue"
    },
    {
      "question": "the local environment",
      "answer": "parts"
    },
    {
      "question": "achieve harmony of opinion, feeling, or purpose",
      "answer": "agree"
    },
    {
      "question": "without distinction of one from others",
      "answer": "generally"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a relaxed manner",
      "answer": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "place on board a ship",
      "answer": "ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "institute legal proceedings against",
      "answer": "action"
    },
    {
      "question": "fasten with stays  ",
      "answer": "stay"
    },
    {
      "question": "furnish with a hat   ",
      "answer": "hat"
    },
    {
      "question": "any movable articles or objects used on the set of a play or movie",
      "answer": "property"
    },
    {
      "question": "physically and mentally sound or healthy",
      "answer": "fit"
    },
    {
      "question": "any hostile group of people",
      "answer": "enemy"
    },
    {
      "question": "to a great degree or by a great distance",
      "answer": "way"
    },
    {
      "question": "brought into existence",
      "answer": "born"
    },
    {
      "question": "used of persons or their behavior",
      "answer": "impossible"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality that renders something desirable or valuable or useful  ",
      "answer": "worth"
    },
    {
      "question": "give occasion to  ",
      "answer": "occasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "be left",
      "answer": "remain"
    },
    {
      "question": "used in polite request",
      "answer": "please"
    },
    {
      "question": "looking pale and unhealthy",
      "answer": "green"
    },
    {
      "question": "joined in matrimony",
      "answer": "married"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the third place",
      "answer": "third"
    },
    {
      "question": "touch with the mouth  ",
      "answer": "mouth"
    },
    {
      "question": "be able to accommodate for sleeping",
      "answer": "sleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "a punctuation mark (.) placed at the end of a declarative sentence to indicate a full stop or after abbreviations",
      "answer": "period"
    },
    {
      "question": "improperly forward or bold",
      "answer": "fresh"
    },
    {
      "question": "loyalty or allegiance to a cause or a person",
      "answer": "faith"
    },
    {
      "question": "the living body considered as made up of interdependent components forming a unified whole",
      "answer": "system"
    },
    {
      "question": "the activity of putting something in written form",
      "answer": "writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "to or toward that place",
      "answer": "there"
    },
    {
      "question": "without any others being included or involved",
      "answer": "entirely"
    },
    {
      "question": "moving or appearing to move away from a place, especially one that is enclosed or hidden",
      "answer": "out"
    },
    {
      "question": "express with a smile",
      "answer": "smile"
    },
    {
      "question": "occurring or encountered or experienced or observed frequently or in accordance with regular practice or procedure",
      "answer": "usual"
    },
    {
      "question": "overlaid or spread or topped with or enclosed within something",
      "answer": "covered"
    },
    {
      "question": "pretending that something is the case in order to make a good impression",
      "answer": "appearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "bound by an oath",
      "answer": "bound"
    },
    {
      "question": "show respect towards",
      "answer": "respect"
    },
    {
      "question": "of the sun characterized by a low level of surface phenomena like sunspots e.g.  ",
      "answer": "quiet"
    },
    {
      "question": "a party of people assembled to have dinner together",
      "answer": "dinner"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of forcing something out by squeezing or pressing",
      "answer": "expression"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of a nose) blocked",
      "answer": "stopped"
    },
    {
      "question": "without speed (`slow' is sometimes used informally for `slowly')",
      "answer": "slowly"
    },
    {
      "question": "large or relatively large in number or amount or extent or degree",
      "answer": "considerable"
    },
    {
      "question": "take a walk",
      "answer": "walk"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a different direction",
      "answer": "away"
    },
    {
      "question": "be amazed at",
      "answer": "wonder"
    },
    {
      "question": "highest in quality  ",
      "answer": "greatest"
    },
    {
      "question": "take measures in preparation for",
      "answer": "provide"
    },
    {
      "question": "precisely accurate or exact",
      "answer": "perfect"
    },
    {
      "question": "engage in social activities leading to marriage",
      "answer": "court"
    },
    {
      "question": "the freshness and vitality characteristic of a young person  ",
      "answer": "youth"
    },
    {
      "question": "require to lose, suffer, or sacrifice",
      "answer": "cost"
    },
    {
      "question": "happening without warning or in a short space of time",
      "answer": "sudden"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the nature of vice  ",
      "answer": "evil"
    },
    {
      "question": "a dangerous place",
      "answer": "danger"
    },
    {
      "question": "a principal pipe in a system that distributes water or gas or electricity or that collects sewage  ",
      "answer": "main"
    },
    {
      "question": "battle or contend against in or as if in a battle",
      "answer": "battle"
    },
    {
      "question": "demand as one's due",
      "answer": "command"
    },
    {
      "question": "express recognition of the presence or existence of, or acquaintance with",
      "answer": "notice"
    },
    {
      "question": "repair by adding pieces",
      "answer": "piece"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the profession of governing",
      "answer": "political"
    },
    {
      "question": "a female person who is a fellow member of a sorority or labor union or other group",
      "answer": "sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "hard to endure",
      "answer": "trying"
    },
    {
      "question": "appropriate for a condition or purpose or occasion or a person's character, needs",
      "answer": "proper"
    },
    {
      "question": "carefully weighed",
      "answer": "considered"
    },
    {
      "question": "considered likely or probable to happen or arrive",
      "answer": "expected"
    },
    {
      "question": "something or someone that provides a source of happiness",
      "answer": "joy"
    },
    {
      "question": "concerning things deeply private and personal",
      "answer": "private"
    },
    {
      "question": "full or promise",
      "answer": "bright"
    },
    {
      "question": "come about or follow as a consequence",
      "answer": "result"
    },
    {
      "question": "swim in or form a large group of fish",
      "answer": "school"
    },
    {
      "question": "serve in a specific professional capacity",
      "answer": "sit"
    },
    {
      "question": "the mental faculty or power of vocal communication",
      "answer": "language"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic of or meant for a single person or thing",
      "answer": "individual"
    },
    {
      "question": "anything that provides mental stimulus for thinking  ",
      "answer": "food"
    },
    {
      "question": "to or over a great extent or range",
      "answer": "wide"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the immediate past",
      "answer": "now"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or given a form or shape  ",
      "answer": "formed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a period of seven consecutive days starting on Sunday  ",
      "answer": "week"
    },
    {
      "question": "all of the living human inhabitants of the earth",
      "answer": "world"
    },
    {
      "question": "being one more than six  ",
      "answer": "seven"
    },
    {
      "question": "a possibility due to a favorable combination of circumstances",
      "answer": "opportunity"
    },
    {
      "question": "fix or determine the value of",
      "answer": "value"
    },
    {
      "question": "being and remaining ready and available for use",
      "answer": "waiting"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking funds",
      "answer": "broke"
    },
    {
      "question": "play a subordinate role to (another performer)",
      "answer": "support"
    },
    {
      "question": "directly or exactly",
      "answer": "due"
    },
    {
      "question": "a settlement smaller than a town  ",
      "answer": "village"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a strenuous or labored effort",
      "answer": "fight"
    },
    {
      "question": "go through (mental or physical states or experiences)",
      "answer": "experience"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of measuring with meters or similar instruments",
      "answer": "reading"
    },
    {
      "question": "(meat) cooked until there is just a little pink meat inside  ",
      "answer": "medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "of any of various dull tannish or grey colors  ",
      "answer": "stone"
    },
    {
      "question": "begin to speak, understand, read, and write a language",
      "answer": "begin"
    },
    {
      "question": "(usually followed by `that') to an extent or degree as expressed",
      "answer": "so"
    },
    {
      "question": "being a single entity made by combining separate components",
      "answer": "one"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person's financial situation (good or bad)",
      "answer": "circumstances"
    },
    {
      "question": "(mathematics) the set of values of the independent variable for which a function is defined  ",
      "answer": "domain"
    },
    {
      "question": "indicating grammatical person",
      "answer": "personal"
    },
    {
      "question": "reach or gain access to",
      "answer": "access"
    },
    {
      "question": "the utterance of intelligible speech  ",
      "answer": "speaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "be a student of a certain subject",
      "answer": "learn"
    },
    {
      "question": "not moving and therefore easy to attack",
      "answer": "sitting"
    },
    {
      "question": "the most important and magnificent in adornment",
      "answer": "grand"
    },
    {
      "question": "the fashionable elite  ",
      "answer": "society"
    },
    {
      "question": "ride in a boat on water  ",
      "answer": "boat"
    },
    {
      "question": "guide or conduct or usher somewhere",
      "answer": "hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide with a dateline",
      "answer": "date"
    },
    {
      "question": "not derived or copied or translated from something else",
      "answer": "original"
    },
    {
      "question": "to a later time",
      "answer": "up"
    },
    {
      "question": "not easy",
      "answer": "difficult"
    },
    {
      "question": "the use of speech for informal exchange of views or ideas or information etc.  ",
      "answer": "conversation"
    },
    {
      "question": "serve as a waiter or waitress in a restaurant",
      "answer": "wait"
    },
    {
      "question": "stretch (a shoe) on a shoetree  ",
      "answer": "tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "write paragraphs",
      "answer": "paragraph"
    },
    {
      "question": "form by pouring (e.g., wax or hot metal) into a cast or mold",
      "answer": "cast"
    },
    {
      "question": "a time unit of approximately 30 days",
      "answer": "month"
    },
    {
      "question": "finish up or conclude",
      "answer": "top"
    },
    {
      "question": "give a healthy elasticity to",
      "answer": "tone"
    },
    {
      "question": "future",
      "answer": "intended"
    },
    {
      "question": "determined or decided upon as by an authority",
      "answer": "determined"
    },
    {
      "question": "move or proceed as if by steps into a new situation",
      "answer": "step"
    },
    {
      "question": "a message describing how something is to be done",
      "answer": "direction"
    },
    {
      "question": "informal information of any kind that is not previously known to someone",
      "answer": "news"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a frequency below or above the range of human audibility",
      "answer": "silent"
    },
    {
      "question": "bring onto the market or release",
      "answer": "produce"
    },
    {
      "question": "being one more than seven  ",
      "answer": "eight"
    },
    {
      "question": "equipped or prepared with necessary intellectual resources",
      "answer": "prepared"
    },
    {
      "question": "have a place in relation to something else",
      "answer": "lie"
    },
    {
      "question": "graphic art consisting of the graphic or photographic representation of a visual percept",
      "answer": "scene"
    },
    {
      "question": "use of physical or mental energy",
      "answer": "effort"
    },
    {
      "question": "earnest and conscientious activity intended to do or accomplish something",
      "answer": "attempt"
    },
    {
      "question": "within the realm of credibility",
      "answer": "likely"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the curtains or draperies closed or pulled shut",
      "answer": "drawn"
    },
    {
      "question": "being ten more than forty  ",
      "answer": "fifty"
    },
    {
      "question": "firmly or closely",
      "answer": "fast"
    },
    {
      "question": "people living or working on the same street",
      "answer": "street"
    },
    {
      "question": "surround with a wall in order to fortify  ",
      "answer": "wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "the activity of shaping something on a lathe  ",
      "answer": "turning"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic of present-day art and music and literature and architecture  ",
      "answer": "modern"
    },
    {
      "question": "associated with or performed by members of the armed services as contrasted with civilians",
      "answer": "military"
    },
    {
      "question": "be the author of",
      "answer": "author"
    },
    {
      "question": "select (a team or individual player) for a game",
      "answer": "field"
    },
    {
      "question": "an interest in land capable of being inherited  ",
      "answer": "fee"
    },
    {
      "question": "feeling pleasurable satisfaction over something by which you measures your self-worth",
      "answer": "pleased"
    },
    {
      "question": "with rapid movements",
      "answer": "quickly"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a perfect or faultless way",
      "answer": "perfectly"
    },
    {
      "question": "an authoritative written work",
      "answer": "authority"
    },
    {
      "question": "not brilliant or glaring",
      "answer": "soft"
    },
    {
      "question": "the cutting part of a drill",
      "answer": "bit"
    },
    {
      "question": "act or preside as chair, as of an academic department in a university",
      "answer": "chair"
    },
    {
      "question": "bring into a particular state by crying",
      "answer": "cry"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by excited activity",
      "answer": "hot"
    },
    {
      "question": "success in satisfying a test or requirement",
      "answer": "passing"
    },
    {
      "question": "opinion or judgment",
      "answer": "eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "spend the summer",
      "answer": "summer"
    },
    {
      "question": "the part of the day between noon and evening",
      "answer": "afternoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "allow the presence of or allow (an activity) without opposing or prohibiting",
      "answer": "allow"
    },
    {
      "question": "declared as fact",
      "answer": "declared"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of passing something to another person  ",
      "answer": "passage"
    },
    {
      "question": "punishment for one's actions",
      "answer": "music"
    },
    {
      "question": "show in, or as in, a picture",
      "answer": "picture"
    },
    {
      "question": "absolutely",
      "answer": "simply"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of persons) having pleasing manners or behavior",
      "answer": "pleasant"
    },
    {
      "question": "incapable of being changed or moved or undone",
      "answer": "fixed"
    },
    {
      "question": "approval to do something",
      "answer": "permission"
    },
    {
      "question": "the exchange of spoken words",
      "answer": "speech"
    },
    {
      "question": "a close and intimate union",
      "answer": "marriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "at this time",
      "answer": "here"
    },
    {
      "question": "think intently and at length, as for spiritual purposes",
      "answer": "study"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to move fast or to rush or race",
      "answer": "race"
    },
    {
      "question": "extremely scrupulous and conscientious",
      "answer": "religious"
    },
    {
      "question": "with difficulty or inconvenience",
      "answer": "ill"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of a church) given official status as a national or state institution  ",
      "answer": "official"
    },
    {
      "question": "be mathematically distributive  ",
      "answer": "distribute"
    },
    {
      "question": "judgment involved in the determination of rights and the assignment of rewards and punishments  ",
      "answer": "justice"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a straight line",
      "answer": "straight"
    },
    {
      "question": "extend credit to",
      "answer": "trust"
    },
    {
      "question": "weaken or destroy in spirit or body",
      "answer": "break"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the same quantity, value, or measure as another",
      "answer": "equal"
    },
    {
      "question": "worry or cause anxiety in a persistent way",
      "answer": "eat"
    },
    {
      "question": "concerned with material things",
      "answer": "physical"
    },
    {
      "question": "an institution to express belief in a divine power",
      "answer": "religion"
    },
    {
      "question": "observe or determine by looking",
      "answer": "watch"
    },
    {
      "question": "fully apprehended as to purport or meaning or explanation",
      "answer": "understood"
    },
    {
      "question": "leave behind unintentionally",
      "answer": "forget"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a state required for something to function or be effective",
      "answer": "on"
    },
    {
      "question": "in or of the present month",
      "answer": "instant"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a systematic arrangement",
      "answer": "ordered"
    },
    {
      "question": "between an earlier and a later period of time",
      "answer": "middle"
    },
    {
      "question": "commit a sin",
      "answer": "sin"
    },
    {
      "question": "a state of prosperity or fame",
      "answer": "success"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of soaps or cleaning agents) having a substance (an abrasive or filler) added to increase effectiveness",
      "answer": "built"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a lord of someone  ",
      "answer": "lord"
    },
    {
      "question": "your overall circumstances or condition in life (including everything that happens to you)",
      "answer": "fortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or prompted by wisdom or discernment",
      "answer": "wise"
    },
    {
      "question": "psychological rather than physical or tangible in effect",
      "answer": "moral"
    },
    {
      "question": "conformity or harmony",
      "answer": "keeping"
    },
    {
      "question": "the social act of assembling for some common purpose",
      "answer": "meeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "make or work out a plan for",
      "answer": "plan"
    },
    {
      "question": "blocked against entry",
      "answer": "closed"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of administering or being in charge of something",
      "answer": "running"
    },
    {
      "question": "come up, of celestial bodies",
      "answer": "rise"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by friendly companionship with others",
      "answer": "social"
    },
    {
      "question": "estimate the value of",
      "answer": "rate"
    },
    {
      "question": "work in the garden",
      "answer": "garden"
    },
    {
      "question": "travel or traverse (a distance)",
      "answer": "do"
    },
    {
      "question": "changed in constitution or structure or composition by metamorphism",
      "answer": "changed"
    },
    {
      "question": "turn a corner",
      "answer": "corner"
    },
    {
      "question": "the course along which a person has walked or is walking in",
      "answer": "steps"
    },
    {
      "question": "a zone or area resembling an island  ",
      "answer": "island"
    },
    {
      "question": "produce or disclose suddenly or unexpectedly",
      "answer": "spring"
    },
    {
      "question": "threaten to do something",
      "answer": "offer"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause emotional anguish or make miserable",
      "answer": "pain"
    },
    {
      "question": "a golf club with a long shaft used to hit long shots",
      "answer": "wood"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide housing for",
      "answer": "house"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a forthright manner",
      "answer": "directly"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a quantity that can fulfill a need or requirement but without being abundant",
      "answer": "sufficient"
    },
    {
      "question": "emotions experienced when in a state of well-being  ",
      "answer": "happiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of traveling from one place to another  ",
      "answer": "journey"
    },
    {
      "question": "not full or rich",
      "answer": "pale"
    },
    {
      "question": "arrange attractively",
      "answer": "dress"
    },
    {
      "question": "lead musicians in the performance of",
      "answer": "conduct"
    },
    {
      "question": "having qualities or abilities that merit recognition in some way",
      "answer": "worthy"
    },
    {
      "question": "be ahead of others",
      "answer": "lead"
    },
    {
      "question": "the deliberate act of deviating from the truth  ",
      "answer": "lying"
    },
    {
      "question": "of great gravity or crucial import",
      "answer": "grave"
    },
    {
      "question": "(sport) the act of controlling the ball (or puck)",
      "answer": "possession"
    },
    {
      "question": "allowed by official rules",
      "answer": "legal"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to drop or sink",
      "answer": "lower"
    },
    {
      "question": "adapted to or reserved for a particular purpose",
      "answer": "special"
    },
    {
      "question": "very unusual",
      "answer": "other"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to stop",
      "answer": "stop"
    },
    {
      "question": "the time between sunset and midnight",
      "answer": "night"
    },
    {
      "question": "a federation of tribes (especially Native American tribes)",
      "answer": "nation"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a seeker",
      "answer": "warm"
    },
    {
      "question": "the seriousness of something (e.g., a burn or crime)",
      "answer": "degree"
    },
    {
      "question": "the area of cognitive psychology that studies memory processes",
      "answer": "memory"
    },
    {
      "question": "give grounds for expectations",
      "answer": "promise"
    },
    {
      "question": "a complex or critical or unusual difficulty",
      "answer": "situation"
    },
    {
      "question": "uttered through the medium of speech or characterized by speech",
      "answer": "spoken"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or originating in or characteristic of another place or part of the world",
      "answer": "foreign"
    },
    {
      "question": "informal terms for a mother  ",
      "answer": "ma"
    },
    {
      "question": "issue or leak, as from a small opening",
      "answer": "escape"
    },
    {
      "question": "the purpose of achieving or obtaining",
      "answer": "sake"
    },
    {
      "question": "the amount by which the cost of a business exceeds its revenue",
      "answer": "loss"
    },
    {
      "question": "established beyond doubt",
      "answer": "proved"
    },
    {
      "question": "to or toward the inside of",
      "answer": "in"
    },
    {
      "question": "having come or been brought to a conclusion",
      "answer": "complete"
    },
    {
      "question": "a feeling of strong sexual desire  ",
      "answer": "passion"
    },
    {
      "question": "informal words for any attempt or effort",
      "answer": "shot"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being difficult",
      "answer": "difficulty"
    },
    {
      "question": "a quality of spirit that enables you to face danger or pain without showing fear  ",
      "answer": "courage"
    },
    {
      "question": "made necessary by an unexpected situation or emergency",
      "answer": "forced"
    },
    {
      "question": "not exceptional in any way especially in quality or ability or size or degree",
      "answer": "ordinary"
    },
    {
      "question": "(Southern regional intensive) very",
      "answer": "mighty"
    },
    {
      "question": "killed in battle",
      "answer": "fallen"
    },
    {
      "question": "as found in nature in the elemental form",
      "answer": "native"
    },
    {
      "question": "comparative of much",
      "answer": "more"
    },
    {
      "question": "generally approved or compelling recognition",
      "answer": "accepted"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide food and lodging (for)",
      "answer": "board"
    },
    {
      "question": "requiring effort or concentration",
      "answer": "serious"
    },
    {
      "question": "prepared or arranged for a meal",
      "answer": "spread"
    },
    {
      "question": "structure consisting of a sloping way down to the water from the place where ships are built or repaired  ",
      "answer": "ways"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or as if having an identifying mark or a mark as specified",
      "answer": "marked"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover the front or surface of",
      "answer": "face"
    },
    {
      "question": "mark with a spot or spots so as to allow easy recognition",
      "answer": "spot"
    },
    {
      "question": "denoting a quantity consisting of 12 items or units  ",
      "answer": "twelve"
    },
    {
      "question": "stop (someone or something) from doing something or being in a certain state",
      "answer": "prevent"
    },
    {
      "question": "look forward to the birth of a child",
      "answer": "expect"
    },
    {
      "question": "providing sophisticated amusement by virtue of having artificially (and vulgarly) mannered or banal or sentimental qualities",
      "answer": "camp"
    },
    {
      "question": "propose formally",
      "answer": "move"
    },
    {
      "question": "spend the winter",
      "answer": "winter"
    },
    {
      "question": "very good;of the highest quality",
      "answer": "excellent"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a charge against or accuse",
      "answer": "tax"
    },
    {
      "question": "regard or treat with consideration, respect, and esteem",
      "answer": "consider"
    },
    {
      "question": "where passengers ride up and down",
      "answer": "car"
    },
    {
      "question": "the commercial activity of transporting and selling goods from a producer to a consumer  ",
      "answer": "distribution"
    },
    {
      "question": "punishment intended as a warning to others",
      "answer": "example"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the white lustrous sheen of silver",
      "answer": "silver"
    },
    {
      "question": "put in a glass container  ",
      "answer": "glass"
    },
    {
      "question": "communicate",
      "answer": "share"
    },
    {
      "question": "a period of 100 years  ",
      "answer": "century"
    },
    {
      "question": "built against or attached to a wall",
      "answer": "engaged"
    },
    {
      "question": "elegance in dress or behavior",
      "answer": "class"
    },
    {
      "question": "bulge outward",
      "answer": "start"
    },
    {
      "question": "a disassembled barrel",
      "answer": "shook"
    },
    {
      "question": "travel by rail or train",
      "answer": "train"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by painstaking care and detailed examination",
      "answer": "minute"
    },
    {
      "question": "divide into lots, as of land, for example  ",
      "answer": "lot"
    },
    {
      "question": "come on stage  ",
      "answer": "enter"
    },
    {
      "question": "specifically or especially distinguished from others",
      "answer": "particularly"
    },
    {
      "question": "to an extraordinary extent or degree",
      "answer": "greatly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a way of doing something, especially a systematic way",
      "answer": "method"
    },
    {
      "question": "after an unspecified period of time or an especially long delay  ",
      "answer": "finally"
    },
    {
      "question": "having curiosity aroused",
      "answer": "curious"
    },
    {
      "question": "altogether different in nature or quality or significance",
      "answer": "opposite"
    },
    {
      "question": "obtain probate of",
      "answer": "prove"
    },
    {
      "question": "represented in words especially with sharpness and detail",
      "answer": "described"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a state of sexual virginity",
      "answer": "pure"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large room in a exchange where the trading is done",
      "answer": "floor"
    },
    {
      "question": "being ten more than twenty  ",
      "answer": "thirty"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove the head of",
      "answer": "head"
    },
    {
      "question": "perceive as familiar",
      "answer": "know"
    },
    {
      "question": "(comparative of `ill') in a less effective or successful or desirable manner",
      "answer": "worse"
    },
    {
      "question": "pay back",
      "answer": "refund"
    },
    {
      "question": "transactions of professional or public interest",
      "answer": "affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person working in the service of another (especially in the household)  ",
      "answer": "servant"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of an undertaking) secure from risk  ",
      "answer": "safe"
    },
    {
      "question": "serving to permit or facilitate further work or activity",
      "answer": "working"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing or fraught with or showing anxiety",
      "answer": "anxious"
    },
    {
      "question": "give medical treatment to  ",
      "answer": "doctor"
    },
    {
      "question": "twisted together",
      "answer": "thrown"
    },
    {
      "question": "the distance or area or volume over which something extends",
      "answer": "extent"
    },
    {
      "question": "very limited in degree",
      "answer": "narrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "be proud of",
      "answer": "pride"
    },
    {
      "question": "a slight movement of the air",
      "answer": "breath"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of words) expressing closely related meanings  ",
      "answer": "similar"
    },
    {
      "question": "come upon or take unawares",
      "answer": "surprise"
    },
    {
      "question": "sing a note with the correct pitch  ",
      "answer": "place"
    },
    {
      "question": "negation of a word or group of words",
      "answer": "not"
    },
    {
      "question": "come into possession of",
      "answer": "obtain"
    },
    {
      "question": "informal term for a man",
      "answer": "dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "press and smooth with a heated iron",
      "answer": "iron"
    },
    {
      "question": "perform a marriage ceremony",
      "answer": "marry"
    },
    {
      "question": "to gather together in large numbers",
      "answer": "crowd"
    },
    {
      "question": "being searched for",
      "answer": "sought"
    },
    {
      "question": "in opposition to a proposition, opinion, etc.",
      "answer": "con"
    },
    {
      "question": "highly educated",
      "answer": "knowing"
    },
    {
      "question": "keep in check",
      "answer": "rule"
    },
    {
      "question": "work as a page",
      "answer": "page"
    },
    {
      "question": "be sexually responsive to, used of a female domesticated mammal",
      "answer": "accept"
    },
    {
      "question": "serve as a shore to",
      "answer": "shore"
    },
    {
      "question": "register the trademark of",
      "answer": "trademark"
    },
    {
      "question": "drink excessive amounts of alcohol",
      "answer": "drink"
    },
    {
      "question": "direct or command as an officer  ",
      "answer": "officer"
    },
    {
      "question": "put on trial or hear a case and sit as the judge at the trial of",
      "answer": "judge"
    },
    {
      "question": "put the ball into play",
      "answer": "serve"
    },
    {
      "question": "begin to injure",
      "answer": "attack"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a northern direction",
      "answer": "north"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of changing the location of something",
      "answer": "movement"
    },
    {
      "question": "the idea that is intended",
      "answer": "meaning"
    },
    {
      "question": "(in Roman numerals, M written with a macron over it) denoting a quantity consisting of 1,000,000 items or units  ",
      "answer": "million"
    },
    {
      "question": "hit at an angle  ",
      "answer": "glance"
    },
    {
      "question": "produce laughter  ",
      "answer": "laugh"
    },
    {
      "question": "exchange or give (something) in exchange for  ",
      "answer": "trade"
    },
    {
      "question": "fail to get or obtain",
      "answer": "lose"
    },
    {
      "question": "subject to a search",
      "answer": "search"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing or characterized by broad-mindedness",
      "answer": "broad"
    },
    {
      "question": "(Christian theology) the free and unmerited favor or beneficence of God",
      "answer": "grace"
    },
    {
      "question": "located far away spatially",
      "answer": "distant"
    },
    {
      "question": "communicate in sign language",
      "answer": "sign"
    },
    {
      "question": "a male member of a royal family other than the sovereign (especially the son of a sovereign)  ",
      "answer": "prince"
    },
    {
      "question": "give an advantage to",
      "answer": "advantage"
    },
    {
      "question": "a significant change",
      "answer": "difference"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an easily perceptible manner",
      "answer": "clearly"
    },
    {
      "question": "gained or earned without cheating or stealing",
      "answer": "honest"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a free manner",
      "answer": "freely"
    },
    {
      "question": "invested with royal power as symbolized by a crown",
      "answer": "royal"
    },
    {
      "question": "arousing or holding the attention  ",
      "answer": "interesting"
    },
    {
      "question": "place in or on a seat",
      "answer": "seat"
    },
    {
      "question": "a line or route along which something travels or moves",
      "answer": "path"
    },
    {
      "question": "feeling self-respect or pleasure in something by which you measure your self-worth",
      "answer": "proud"
    },
    {
      "question": "publicly announced",
      "answer": "posted"
    },
    {
      "question": "brought to ruin",
      "answer": "finished"
    },
    {
      "question": "an area outside of cities and towns",
      "answer": "country"
    },
    {
      "question": "place at intervals",
      "answer": "space"
    },
    {
      "question": "inquire for (information)",
      "answer": "request"
    },
    {
      "question": "to the greatest degree or extent",
      "answer": "fully"
    },
    {
      "question": "of things that make you feel sad",
      "answer": "sad"
    },
    {
      "question": "easily aroused or excited",
      "answer": "quick"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) all the means by which any alleged matter of fact whose truth is investigated at judicial trial is established or disproved  ",
      "answer": "evidence"
    },
    {
      "question": "the atmosphere and outer space as viewed from the earth  ",
      "answer": "sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "not plain",
      "answer": "fancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "see fit or proper to act in a certain way",
      "answer": "choose"
    },
    {
      "question": "be the captain of a sports team  ",
      "answer": "captain"
    },
    {
      "question": "practicing complete abstinence from alcoholic beverages",
      "answer": "dry"
    },
    {
      "question": "experience briefly",
      "answer": "taste"
    },
    {
      "question": "a cutting or thrusting weapon that has a long metal blade and a hilt with a hand guard  ",
      "answer": "sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "a secret that is confided or entrusted to another",
      "answer": "confidence"
    },
    {
      "question": "be tantamount or equivalent to",
      "answer": "amount"
    },
    {
      "question": "the general condition of body and mind",
      "answer": "health"
    },
    {
      "question": "personal freedom from servitude or confinement or oppression  ",
      "answer": "liberty"
    },
    {
      "question": "emotional or moral sensitivity (especially in relation to personal principles or dignity)",
      "answer": "feelings"
    },
    {
      "question": "treat to wine",
      "answer": "wine"
    },
    {
      "question": "newly come into prominence",
      "answer": "rising"
    },
    {
      "question": "not open",
      "answer": "shut"
    },
    {
      "question": "not changeable",
      "answer": "settled"
    },
    {
      "question": "complain about",
      "answer": "report"
    },
    {
      "question": "the set of circumstances that affect someone's welfare",
      "answer": "conditions"
    },
    {
      "question": "not likely to fail or give way",
      "answer": "secure"
    },
    {
      "question": "united by being of the same opinion",
      "answer": "agreed"
    },
    {
      "question": "every day",
      "answer": "daily"
    },
    {
      "question": "inquire for",
      "answer": "seek"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to nationality",
      "answer": "national"
    },
    {
      "question": "great in vertical dimension",
      "answer": "tall"
    },
    {
      "question": "the major party to a financial transaction at a stock exchange",
      "answer": "principal"
    },
    {
      "question": "taking care or paying attention",
      "answer": "carefully"
    },
    {
      "question": "constitute an addition",
      "answer": "add"
    },
    {
      "question": "evaluate or estimate the nature, quality, ability, extent, or significance of",
      "answer": "measure"
    },
    {
      "question": "rejoice proudly  ",
      "answer": "glory"
    },
    {
      "question": "communicated in words",
      "answer": "expressed"
    },
    {
      "question": "to be courageous enough to try or do something",
      "answer": "dare"
    },
    {
      "question": "a prominent status",
      "answer": "importance"
    },
    {
      "question": "markedly different from the usual",
      "answer": "peculiar"
    },
    {
      "question": "the occupants of a building",
      "answer": "building"
    },
    {
      "question": "furnish with people",
      "answer": "people"
    },
    {
      "question": "brightly colored and showy",
      "answer": "brave"
    },
    {
      "question": "an affirmative",
      "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "accept as pay",
      "answer": "honor"
    },
    {
      "question": "experience while sleeping",
      "answer": "dream"
    },
    {
      "question": "a land mass that projects well above its surroundings",
      "answer": "mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "quiet and soothing",
      "answer": "gentle"
    },
    {
      "question": "resided in",
      "answer": "occupied"
    },
    {
      "question": "deeply affected by a strong feeling",
      "answer": "sick"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a southern direction",
      "answer": "south"
    },
    {
      "question": "in quick succession",
      "answer": "thick"
    },
    {
      "question": "develop in a positive way",
      "answer": "progress"
    },
    {
      "question": "a swarthy complexion  ",
      "answer": "darkness"
    },
    {
      "question": "take as an undesirable consequence of some event or state of affairs",
      "answer": "claim"
    },
    {
      "question": "a playing card in the major suit that has one or more red hearts on it",
      "answer": "heart"
    },
    {
      "question": "willing to face danger  ",
      "answer": "game"
    },
    {
      "question": "money to support a worthy person or cause  ",
      "answer": "aid"
    },
    {
      "question": "make cracks or chinks in",
      "answer": "check"
    },
    {
      "question": "performed with little or no delay",
      "answer": "immediate"
    },
    {
      "question": "keep in mind  ",
      "answer": "mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "a form of whist in which players avoid winning tricks containing hearts or the queen of spades  ",
      "answer": "hearts"
    },
    {
      "question": "in reserve",
      "answer": "aside"
    },
    {
      "question": "place in a container for keeping records",
      "answer": "file"
    },
    {
      "question": "resistant to guidance or discipline",
      "answer": "contrary"
    },
    {
      "question": "absurd or silly because unlikely",
      "answer": "fond"
    },
    {
      "question": "the speech act of continuing a conversational exchange",
      "answer": "reply"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to localize at one point",
      "answer": "draw"
    },
    {
      "question": "belonging to or derived from or associated with a divine power  ",
      "answer": "holy"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or suitable for growth",
      "answer": "growing"
    },
    {
      "question": "from first to last",
      "answer": "throughout"
    },
    {
      "question": "the lowest rank",
      "answer": "bottom"
    },
    {
      "question": "spread out or scattered about or divided up  ",
      "answer": "distributed"
    },
    {
      "question": "become attached by or as if by the process of growth",
      "answer": "grow"
    },
    {
      "question": "a living organism characterized by voluntary movement  ",
      "answer": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "going or proceeding or going in advance",
      "answer": "leading"
    },
    {
      "question": "having come into contact  ",
      "answer": "touched"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used especially of persons) not dependable in devotion or affection",
      "answer": "false"
    },
    {
      "question": "reduce the estimated value of something",
      "answer": "expense"
    },
    {
      "question": "informing by words  ",
      "answer": "telling"
    },
    {
      "question": "the capacity to assess situations or circumstances shrewdly and to draw sound conclusions  ",
      "answer": "judgment"
    },
    {
      "question": "amounting to a large indefinite number",
      "answer": "numerous"
    },
    {
      "question": "something that is found",
      "answer": "finding"
    },
    {
      "question": "many times at short intervals",
      "answer": "frequently"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who is controlled by others and is used to perform unpleasant or dishonest tasks for someone else  ",
      "answer": "creature"
    },
    {
      "question": "form into a hill  ",
      "answer": "hill"
    },
    {
      "question": "with everything included or counted",
      "answer": "altogether"
    },
    {
      "question": "without unusual distress or resentment",
      "answer": "well"
    },
    {
      "question": "to the same degree (often followed by `as')",
      "answer": "equally"
    },
    {
      "question": "first or beginning",
      "answer": "opening"
    },
    {
      "question": "in other respects or ways",
      "answer": "otherwise"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of games) engaged in",
      "answer": "played"
    },
    {
      "question": "trace a line through or across",
      "answer": "cross"
    },
    {
      "question": "engaged in full-time work",
      "answer": "active"
    },
    {
      "question": "quick and forceful",
      "answer": "sharp"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover with ashes so to control the rate of burning",
      "answer": "bank"
    },
    {
      "question": "definitely or positively (`sure' is sometimes used informally for `surely')",
      "answer": "surely"
    },
    {
      "question": "rise in rate or price",
      "answer": "advance"
    },
    {
      "question": "uppercase",
      "answer": "capital"
    },
    {
      "question": "disposed or inclined toward",
      "answer": "willing"
    },
    {
      "question": "taken unawares or suddenly and feeling wonder or astonishment",
      "answer": "surprised"
    },
    {
      "question": "a thin curved glass or plastic lens designed to fit over the cornea in order to correct vision or to deliver medication  ",
      "answer": "contact"
    },
    {
      "question": "anything indispensable",
      "answer": "necessity"
    },
    {
      "question": "having great power or force or potency or effect",
      "answer": "powerful"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a natural or normal manner",
      "answer": "naturally"
    },
    {
      "question": "introduced from another region and persisting without cultivation  ",
      "answer": "established"
    },
    {
      "question": "presaging or likely to bring good luck",
      "answer": "golden"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of domestic animals) sexually competent",
      "answer": "entire"
    },
    {
      "question": "appealing to or using the intellect",
      "answer": "intellectual"
    },
    {
      "question": "put to use  ",
      "answer": "employed"
    },
    {
      "question": "destroy a vitally essential quality of or in",
      "answer": "kill"
    },
    {
      "question": "food made from dough of flour or meal and usually raised with yeast or baking powder and then baked  ",
      "answer": "bread"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of a check) marked for deposit only as indicated by having two lines drawn across it  ",
      "answer": "crossed"
    },
    {
      "question": "at this time or period",
      "answer": "presently"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking spirit or sincere effort",
      "answer": "thin"
    },
    {
      "question": "divide, combine, or mark into phrases",
      "answer": "phrase"
    },
    {
      "question": "flow freely and abundantly",
      "answer": "stream"
    },
    {
      "question": "move effortlessly",
      "answer": "coast"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large building for meetings or entertainment  ",
      "answer": "hall"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of music or art) new and of general appeal (especially among young people)  ",
      "answer": "popular"
    },
    {
      "question": "direct and obvious in meaning or reference",
      "answer": "pointed"
    },
    {
      "question": "provided with furnishing and accessories (especially of a tasteful kind)",
      "answer": "appointed"
    },
    {
      "question": "of metal e.g.",
      "answer": "bent"
    },
    {
      "question": "pay no attention to, disrespect",
      "answer": "slight"
    },
    {
      "question": "form a group or group together  ",
      "answer": "group"
    },
    {
      "question": "from appearances alone",
      "answer": "apparently"
    },
    {
      "question": "unusual or striking",
      "answer": "remarkable"
    },
    {
      "question": "any object that is left unused or still extant",
      "answer": "remains"
    },
    {
      "question": "kiss, embrace, or fondle with sexual passion",
      "answer": "neck"
    },
    {
      "question": "land that is covered with trees and shrubs  ",
      "answer": "forest"
    },
    {
      "question": "request an encore, from a performer  ",
      "answer": "encore"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to move back and forth",
      "answer": "rock"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a hole, especially with a pointed power or hand tool",
      "answer": "bore"
    },
    {
      "question": "prepared and printed for distribution and sale",
      "answer": "published"
    },
    {
      "question": "the location of something surrounded by other things",
      "answer": "midst"
    },
    {
      "question": "being of such surpassing excellence as to suggest inspiration by the gods",
      "answer": "divine"
    },
    {
      "question": "a machine part that carries something else  ",
      "answer": "carriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to two people who are married to each other  ",
      "answer": "joined"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of populating (causing to live in a place)",
      "answer": "population"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking compromising or mitigating elements",
      "answer": "direct"
    },
    {
      "question": "property that has economic utility: a monetary value or an exchange value  ",
      "answer": "wealth"
    },
    {
      "question": "lessen pain or discomfort",
      "answer": "comfort"
    },
    {
      "question": "tilt to one side",
      "answer": "list"
    },
    {
      "question": "burst suddenly",
      "answer": "blow"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of plants) not hardy",
      "answer": "tender"
    },
    {
      "question": "an individual that one is not acquainted with  ",
      "answer": "stranger"
    },
    {
      "question": "a specific kind of something",
      "answer": "species"
    },
    {
      "question": "lead up to and soften by sounding the dissonant note in it as a consonant note in the preceding chord",
      "answer": "prepare"
    },
    {
      "question": "(often followed by `to') devoted exclusively to a single use or purpose or person",
      "answer": "sacred"
    },
    {
      "question": "being perceived or observed",
      "answer": "noticed"
    },
    {
      "question": "as a sentence modifier to add slight emphasis",
      "answer": "actually"
    },
    {
      "question": "cowardly or treacherous",
      "answer": "yellow"
    },
    {
      "question": "on the surface",
      "answer": "surface"
    },
    {
      "question": "having important effects or influence",
      "answer": "consequence"
    },
    {
      "question": "an unfortunate development",
      "answer": "pity"
    },
    {
      "question": "throw (a die) out onto a flat surface",
      "answer": "throw"
    },
    {
      "question": "put a habit on  ",
      "answer": "habit"
    },
    {
      "question": "deficient in intelligence or mental power",
      "answer": "weak"
    },
    {
      "question": "used of a person's appearance or behavior",
      "answer": "distinguished"
    },
    {
      "question": "address a deity, a prophet, a saint or an object of worship",
      "answer": "pray"
    },
    {
      "question": "the condition of being free",
      "answer": "freedom"
    },
    {
      "question": "plan, organize, and carry out (an event)",
      "answer": "stage"
    },
    {
      "question": "in repayment or retaliation",
      "answer": "back"
    },
    {
      "question": "severely inflamed and painful",
      "answer": "angry"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of skin) deeply suntanned  ",
      "answer": "brown"
    },
    {
      "question": "filled with satisfaction",
      "answer": "satisfied"
    },
    {
      "question": "precipitate as rain",
      "answer": "rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "by express",
      "answer": "express"
    },
    {
      "question": "rule of personal conduct  ",
      "answer": "principle"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of societies) highly developed especially in technology or industry",
      "answer": "advanced"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who owns something",
      "answer": "owner"
    },
    {
      "question": "depleted of strength or energy",
      "answer": "tired"
    },
    {
      "question": "a writer of poems (the term is usually reserved for writers of good poetry)  ",
      "answer": "poet"
    },
    {
      "question": "avail oneself to",
      "answer": "practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "having mutual interests or affections",
      "answer": "familiar"
    },
    {
      "question": "one of a series of texts for students learning to read  ",
      "answer": "reader"
    },
    {
      "question": "take delight in",
      "answer": "delight"
    },
    {
      "question": "change under the action or influence of the weather",
      "answer": "weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "catch or try to catch fish or shellfish",
      "answer": "fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "denoting a quantity consisting of one more than eight and one less than ten  ",
      "answer": "nine"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or showing interest",
      "answer": "interested"
    },
    {
      "question": "make advances to someone, usually with a proposal or suggestion",
      "answer": "approach"
    },
    {
      "question": "(statistics) a coefficient assigned to elements of a frequency distribution in order to represent their relative importance  ",
      "answer": "weight"
    },
    {
      "question": "in accordance with truth or fact or reality",
      "answer": "truly"
    },
    {
      "question": "concerned with or affecting physical as distinct from intellectual or psychological well-being",
      "answer": "material"
    },
    {
      "question": "to remain unmolested, undisturbed, or uninterrupted -- used only in infinitive form",
      "answer": "be"
    },
    {
      "question": "playing or singing with instrumental or vocal accompaniment   ",
      "answer": "accompanied"
    },
    {
      "question": "damage beyond the point of repair",
      "answer": "total"
    },
    {
      "question": "feed with grass  ",
      "answer": "grass"
    },
    {
      "question": "divide by four",
      "answer": "quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "make consistent with certain rules of style",
      "answer": "style"
    },
    {
      "question": "officially full-time",
      "answer": "regular"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing fear or anxiety by threatening great harm",
      "answer": "dangerous"
    },
    {
      "question": "a very small sum",
      "answer": "song"
    },
    {
      "question": "the result of good upbringing (especially knowledge of correct social behavior)",
      "answer": "education"
    },
    {
      "question": "make appear small by comparison",
      "answer": "shadow"
    },
    {
      "question": "to a complete degree or to the full or entire extent (`whole' is often used informally for `wholly')",
      "answer": "wholly"
    },
    {
      "question": "be capable of holding or containing",
      "answer": "contain"
    },
    {
      "question": "hunting: chase from cover into more open ground",
      "answer": "drive"
    },
    {
      "question": "a particular moral excellence  ",
      "answer": "virtue"
    },
    {
      "question": "make out of components (often in an improvising manner)",
      "answer": "fashion"
    },
    {
      "question": "urged or forced to action through moral pressure",
      "answer": "driven"
    },
    {
      "question": "restrict (school boys') movement to the dormitory or campus as a means of punishment  ",
      "answer": "gate"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of lumber or stone) to trim and smooth  ",
      "answer": "dressed"
    },
    {
      "question": "pronounce a sentence on (somebody) in a court of law",
      "answer": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "question": "two times",
      "answer": "twice"
    },
    {
      "question": "far more than usual or expected",
      "answer": "extraordinary"
    },
    {
      "question": "take precautions in order to avoid some unwanted consequence",
      "answer": "guard"
    },
    {
      "question": "the ability to hear",
      "answer": "hearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "strike (water or bushes) repeatedly to rouse animals for hunting  ",
      "answer": "beat"
    },
    {
      "question": "having much knowledge or education",
      "answer": "informed"
    },
    {
      "question": "break open or apart suddenly and forcefully",
      "answer": "burst"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of weather) free from storm or wind",
      "answer": "calm"
    },
    {
      "question": "join together into a mass or collect or form a mass",
      "answer": "mass"
    },
    {
      "question": "the basic unit of money in Kyrgyzstan  ",
      "answer": "som"
    },
    {
      "question": "ascertain or learn the price of",
      "answer": "price"
    },
    {
      "question": "a particular branch of scientific knowledge",
      "answer": "science"
    },
    {
      "question": "made greater in size or amount or degree  ",
      "answer": "increased"
    },
    {
      "question": "given medical care or treatment",
      "answer": "treated"
    },
    {
      "question": "express gratitude or show appreciation to  ",
      "answer": "thank"
    },
    {
      "question": "see for the first time",
      "answer": "discover"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a base of operations (often used as a combining form)",
      "answer": "based"
    },
    {
      "question": "gain heat or get hot",
      "answer": "heat"
    },
    {
      "question": "fruiting spike of a cereal plant especially corn  ",
      "answer": "ear"
    },
    {
      "question": "adjust and aim (a golf ball) at in preparation of hitting  ",
      "answer": "address"
    },
    {
      "question": "exceptional creative ability  ",
      "answer": "genius"
    },
    {
      "question": "steadfast in purpose or devotion or affection",
      "answer": "constant"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of causing something to go (especially messages)  ",
      "answer": "sending"
    },
    {
      "question": "form a mental image of something that is not present or that is not the case",
      "answer": "imagine"
    },
    {
      "question": "guess correctly",
      "answer": "guess"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of pressing one thing on or into the surface of another",
      "answer": "impression"
    },
    {
      "question": "a source of help and advice and encouragement",
      "answer": "uncle"
    },
    {
      "question": "a long depression in the surface of the land that usually contains a river  ",
      "answer": "valley"
    },
    {
      "question": "fall as snow",
      "answer": "snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "not known to exist",
      "answer": "unknown"
    },
    {
      "question": "a document showing credits and debits  ",
      "answer": "statement"
    },
    {
      "question": "act in accordance with someone's rules, commands, or wishes",
      "answer": "comply"
    },
    {
      "question": "make by machinery",
      "answer": "machine"
    },
    {
      "question": "appealing to the emotions as well as the eye  ",
      "answer": "lovely"
    },
    {
      "question": "be set at a disadvantage",
      "answer": "suffer"
    },
    {
      "question": "to or at a greater distance in time or space (`farther' is used more frequently than `further' in this physical sense)",
      "answer": "farther"
    },
    {
      "question": "with little or no activity or no agitation (`quiet' is a nonstandard variant for `quietly')",
      "answer": "quietly"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an inactive or inoperative state",
      "answer": "down"
    },
    {
      "question": "growing profusely",
      "answer": "rank"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who arrives (or has arrived)  ",
      "answer": "arrival"
    },
    {
      "question": "necessary for relief or supply",
      "answer": "needed"
    },
    {
      "question": "lick or explore with the tongue  ",
      "answer": "tongue"
    },
    {
      "question": "mutual dealings or connections or communications among persons or groups  ",
      "answer": "relations"
    },
    {
      "question": "totally and definitely",
      "answer": "absolutely"
    },
    {
      "question": "not to be altered or undone",
      "answer": "final"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide with an edge",
      "answer": "edge"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by or producing sound of great volume or intensity",
      "answer": "loud"
    },
    {
      "question": "(followed by `of') having the temperament or inclination for",
      "answer": "capable"
    },
    {
      "question": "expose one's buttocks to",
      "answer": "moon"
    },
    {
      "question": "commend",
      "answer": "mention"
    },
    {
      "question": "engage in a boxing match  ",
      "answer": "box"
    },
    {
      "question": "to exert strenuous effort against opposition",
      "answer": "struggle"
    },
    {
      "question": "make fit",
      "answer": "season"
    },
    {
      "question": "people who are wounded",
      "answer": "wounded"
    },
    {
      "question": "two together",
      "answer": "double"
    },
    {
      "question": "to, toward, or in the west",
      "answer": "west"
    }
  ]
}